(Sheldon:)That's Northwest Texas.
I'm from East Texas, the Gulf region...
(Sheldon:)...home to many Vietnamese shrimpers.
(Leonard:)Do the shrimpers feature in your story?
(Howard:)No.
Anyway, when I was 8...
...a Montgomery Ward delivery van
ran over our family cat, Lucky.
- "Lucky"?
- Yes, "Lucky."
(Leonard:)He's irony impaired. Just move on.
(Howard:)Okay, dead cat named Lucky. Continue.
(Sheldon:)While others mourned Lucky...
...I realized his untimely demise provided
me with the opportunity to replace him...
(Sheldon:)...with something
more suited to my pet needs.
(Sheldon:)A faithful companion
that I could snuggle with at night...
(Sheldon:)...yet would be capable of killing
upon telepathic command.
(Howard:)So not a puppy?
(Sheldon:)Please. No, nothing so pedestrian.
(Sheldon:)I wanted a griffin.
- A griffin?
- Yes, half eagle, half lion.